quickhit.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Majesco Entertainment

Majesco Entertainment ("Majesco" or “we” “our” or “us”) respects the privacy rights of our online visitors and is committed to protecting the information collected from you. To further this commitment, we have adopted an online privacy policy ("privacy policy") that guides how we collect, use, and disclose the information you provide to Majesco online. If you are a parent or legal guardian and are interested in knowing more about Majesco's policy regarding the collection of information from children under 13, please see our children's section below.  This privacy policy currently applies to websites operated by Majesco with a link to this policy (collectively referred to as "this website" or "our website")

Please note that this privacy policy applies only to information submitted and collected online through the websites, and does not apply to information that may be collected by Majesco offline. In addition, this privacy policy applies to Majesco only, and not to websites maintained by our international affiliates (e.g., Majesco UK) or by other companies or organizations to which we link. When you link to these websites or to any other sites from a website operated by Majesco (as listed above), this privacy policy no longer applies.

#####  ** _What types of information does Majesco collect and how will it be used?_**

In order to give you the best experience on our website, Majesco may collect information about you. We may ask a user to submit personal and/or demographic information in connection with the following activities:

  * Game specific websites
  * Registration
  * Subscription to an electronic newsletter
  * Participation in online contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions
  * Accounts necessary to use some of our games. 

Personal information collected in conjunction with these activities includes identifying information about you and/or information that could be used to contact you and may include your first and last name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, Internet Protocol (IP) address, photos/videos/audio files and geolocation information. For some activities, we may ask you to create a username and password and to provide other non-personal information such as your age or date of birth, gender, game and platform preferences, and other interests (also known as "demographic information"); and, if collected on a form that also requests personal information, combine such information with your personal information.

In some cases, we may require financial information to make a purchase or for other puposes.  When we collect credit card information online, we will use protective technologies such as SSL encryption to help protect such information.

We may use information that we collect for the particular purpose you provided us the information. For example, if you sign up for our newsletter, the email address that you provide will be used to send you, via email, updates regarding new products, special offers, and other events of interest. Similarly, information collected from those who register on our website is used to provide registrants the benefits that come along with registration, which often include a subscription to our newsletter, product/customer support, and participation in promotions and other activities. In some instances, however, you may also be given the option to have your information used for an activity or service different from the activity or service that you are requesting (e.g., to have your name entered into a contest when subscribing to our newsletter and vice versa). If you choose to receive these additional services, Majesco will use your information to carry out such services.

We may also use the personal and/or demographic information collected through one of the activities set forth above for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the online products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs.

We may also take information you provide use and combine it with other publicly available information about you.

Please note that we are prohibited from conditioning participation in an activity on users disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that activity (i.e. requiring a Social Security number for an online contest). 

#####  ** _What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information to Majesco?_**

If you choose not to submit personal information when requested, you may not be able to participate in certain activities on our website and may limit the services we can provide you. For example, if you refuse to provide your email address to us, you will not be able to register on our site or receive our electronic newsletter. To simply browse our website, however, you do not need to give us any personal information.

#####  **Technical Information  **

######  **Log Data  **

When you visit the website, our servers (or servers controlled by our third party service providers) may automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address, operating system, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our website, pages of our website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our website, access times and dates, and other statistics and technical data. If Log Data is collected, we may use this information for any purpose including, without limitation, to monitor and analyze use of the website and for the website's technical administration, to increase our website's functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor the website to our visitors' needs.  We do not treat Log Data as personal information.

#####  **Cookies, web beacons, and related technology**

Like many online services, we and our third party service providers may use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we or a third party may transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We or a third party may use cookies to enable certain features of the website, to better understand how you interact with the website and to monitor aggregate usage by visitors and web traffic routing on the website. Third parties providing content on the website may also place or read cookies on your browser. We also use third-party cookies that demonstrate your interest in our website.  These cookies will allow advertising on other websites to better match your interests, including interests in our website.  You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the website or all functionality of the website.  We may also use other technical tracking mechanisms such as web beacons and retargeting associated with our marketing efforts.  These technologies allow us to know when you have viewed our website or read our communications and may also allow us to advertise to you on third-party sites.  We also use cookie technology to aid in our age screening and ensuring legal compliance.  

#####  ** _Who is collecting my personal information?_**

The information that you disclose while visiting our website is collected by Majesco or by a vendor on Majesco's behalf, and is used in accordance with the practices set forth above.

#####  ** _With whom does Majesco share my personal information?_**

Majesco may employ and share your personal information with entities that provide support for the internal operations of our website (e.g., registration fulfillment and newsletter delivery). 

From time to time, we may offer contests, sweepstakes, or promotions ("promotion") to our online visitors. Information collected for these events typically include personal information such as your email address. While we have no control over the third party's use of such information, we will attempt to ensure that they agree to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of any personal information collected through our website. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party, you can choose not to participate in promotions offered on our site.

We may provide information to third parties to aid with our advertising initiatives. 

We may also disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are required to do so by law, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with legal processes, respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of Majesco, our customers, or the public. In addition, information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed to a third party as part of any bankruptcy, merger, sale, transfer of company assets, acquisition, or similar event, if permitted by and done in accordance with applicable law.

#####  ** _What is Majesco's policy regarding links to third party sites?_**

You should be aware that while you are on Services operated by Majesco, you may be directed to other sites that are beyond our control and for which we are not responsible. Because we cannot guarantee that the privacy policies of these websites meet our high standards, we recommend that you read the privacy policy of the website to which you link before you submit any personal information.

#####  ** _Can I choose how my personal information is used?_**

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or information about our products and services, you can opt-out from receiving such communications by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each newsletter email. Alternatively, you may write to our privacy policy administrator at the address provided below for any request. We will be happy to honor your request.

#####  ** _How can I access my personal information?_**

If you wish to review, update, or delete any other personal information that we may have collected about you (e.g., for purposes of registration), please contact our marketing department in writing at the address provided below.  If the website you are using has an account feature with a username and password, you can also update certain personal information using the account functions on the website.

######  **Public Forums**

Certain areas of our website are public, such as our forums.  Any information you post in those public areas are made public and are viewable by anyone.  Majesco cautions you to use good judgment when posting in any public area.

#####  ** _What is Majesco's online privacy policy regarding children under 13?_**

We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children and encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of online activities regularly. We comply with COPPA whenever collecting any information for any under the age of 13 for our child directed games and other Services.

######  **Use of children's personal information**

Information collected from children in the context of an e-card, contest, or other similar one-time event is used solely for the purpose of fulfilling the child 's request and is subsequently deleted. Any personal information that a child provides to our Services for purposes of a newsletter subscription or otherwise is collected by Majesco or by a vendor on our behalf, can only be collected with a parent's approval in compliance with COPPA.

If you are the parent of a child, you can contact Majesco at the address below and Majesco will make reasonable efforts to accommodate any request you have related to your child’s information, including removing any information we have on your child from our marketing databases. 

#####  ** _What safeguards does Majesco use to protect my personal information?_**

We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect personal information from unauthorized access.  Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. 

######  **Our website is in the United States**

Our website is operated out of the United Sates.  By using this website, you agree that your information may be exported to, processed, and stored in the United States.

#####  ** _How do I ask a question or file a complaint?  _**

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this privacy policy or our information collection practices, please contact Majesco by regular mail at:

 **Majesco Entertainment**  
Attn: Marketing Department  
160 Raritan Center Parkway  
Edison, NJ 08837

Or contact us via email at: marketing@majescoent.com
